1800accountant.com 2015-03-14

# Privacy Policy Effective Date: December 1, 2014

                                                 Privacy Policy
Effective Date: December 1, 2014
Introduction
1800Accountant and its affiliates, (collectively, "1800Accountant") reserves the right to change this Privacy
Policy from time to time at its sole discretion and without sending notice to you, so you should review this
Privacy Policy periodically. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that
we have about you and your account. will not materially change our policies and practices to make them less
protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
This Privacy Policy does not govern third party products, services or sites: they are not controlled by
1800Accountant, and may have different terms of use and privacy policies, which 1800Accountant
encourages you to review.
Personal Information that We Collect and How We Use It
1800Accountant’s policy is to protect the confidentiality of the individually identifiable information that you
provide in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 1800Accountant collects the following information from you:
Name, Address, Phone Number, Email Address. In addition, if you choose to complete certain forms or send
us requests, you will be asked to provide the following information: full name, street address, city, state ZIP,
phone number, e- mail address, credit card number, geolocation information. You can review and change to
personal information by clicking on “My Account” and making any changes.
1800Accountant’s policy is to prohibit the unlawful disclosure of your personal information. 1800Accountant
may provide information to its affiliates as permitted by law, including for purposes of responding to your
requests to receive information or services offered by those affiliates. 1800Accountant may disclose
personally identifiable information you provide to third parties if (i) you opt in (consent) to such disclosure;
(ii) we are required to do so by law or (iii) in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is
reasonably necessary to: (a) complete the sales transaction, such as providing your shipping information to
our carrier; (b) comply with legal process; (c) enforce our Terms of Service; (d) respond to claims that any
information you provide violates the rights of third parties; (e) protect the rights, property, or personal safety
of 1800Accountant, its users and/or the public; or (f) in the event that all or substantially all of
1800Accountant’s assets are acquired by a third party. Except as provided in the preceding sentence,
1800Accountant will NOT share, sell or trade your personally identifiable information with third parties, such
as sellers of goods or services.
Mailing List
1800Accountant encourages all users of this Site to register for the mailing list, so that you can receive the
latest tax and accounting news and information as well as updates on our newest products and services. You
may unsubscribe at any time by calling 800-222-6868.
What Other Information We Collect
1800Accountant logs your current Internet address (this is usually a temporary address assigned by your
Internet service provider when you log in), the type of operating system you are using, and the type of
browser software used. In addition, 1800Accountant may keep track of what portions of this Site you are
visiting. 1800Accountant aggregates this information to help 1800Accountant improve or create a better
experience for users of the Site. For example: 1800Accountant may upgrade those parts of the Site that are
heavily visited.

Our website automatically records website usage information that we analyze statistically to track
operational problems, to prevent fraud and to improve the effectiveness, security and integrity of the site. We
do not use this information to track or record information about individuals. We will disclose this information
to third parties only in aggregate form or as may be required by law. For each page that you visit, we collect
and store the following technical information in what is called a web server log file:
 Date and tim e of access
 URL address of the 1800Accountant webpagevisited
 Inter net dom ain and IP address from which our w ebsite was accessed
 Type of browser and oper ating system used to access our site (if provided by the browser)
 URL address of the referring page (if provided by the browser)
 Com pletion or success status of the request for a web page or other on-line item
 File size of the w ebpage visited
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of information that a web site sends to your computer, which is stored in a file on your
computer’s hard drive. A cookie does not tell us your individual identity unless you have chosen to provide it
to us. Most cookies expire after a defined period of time (a “session cookie”).
For the purpose of enabling better website design and a better user experience, we employ Google Analytics
(a web service by Google, Inc.) to track site traffic and provide aggregate reports of how the public interacts
with our website. Session cookies are employed by Google Analytics in the form of client-side JavaScript code.
In utilizing this analytics service, 1800Accountant maintains its existing standards in regards to the sharing
and disclosure of information, security and privacy safeguards for the data, and the data retention policy,
each described below. Google Analytics analyzes website usage information automatically upon visits to the
1800Accountant website(s). Users who do not wish to have their visit information collected by Google
Analytics may opt-out by downloading a browser extension or by disabling cookies in their browser settings.
Opting-out of web measurements will still permit users to access the full 1800Accountant website, with all
included information and functionality.
Tracking
1800Accountant will not recognize Web browser “do not track” signals. If you would like additional
information about online tracking and various opt-out mechanisms, please see http://donottrack.us/
Because we link to social media sites, and from time to time may include third-party advertisements, other
parties may collect your personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across
different web sites when you visit this Site.
Encryption
1800Accountant uses no encryption (data scrambling) on certain portions of the Site, but uses encryption on
portions where you are transmitting financial information, such as credit card information. When you are on
any web site that asks you for confidential information, you should check to see if the information being
transmitted is encrypted in order to increase the security of your information. Keep in mind that there is no
such thing as perfect security.

Children and Minors
1800Accountant makes no active effort to collect personal information from children under the age of 18 and
does not wish to receive any such information.
Contact Us
For further information on Privacy matters contact Lindsay Kush lkush@1800accountant.com
Your Privacy Rights for California Residents
California residents who have elected to provide us personal information in obtaining products or services
for personal, family or household use have a right to request and obtain from us once a calendar year
information about the customer information we have shared, if any, with other businesses for their own
direct marketing uses. This information would include the categories of customer information specified in the
California “Shine the Light” law, and we will also provide the names and addresses of those businesses with
which we shared customer information for the immediately preceding calendar year. To obtain this
information, California residents should send an email to Lindsay Kush lkush@mytaxservice.com with
“Request for California Privacy Rights Info” on the subject line. We will provide the requested information to
you at the email address you provide for a response.
